The user interface has been updated. The user interface has been redesigned, and the layout will be more concise and intuitive. You can freely separate, integrate, and re-arrange each window.
You can also save or add customized interface layout.
The window has also been updated. There are larger icons and simpler layout.
You can easily switch between Connect Shop, Closet, and default assets.
Click the icon in the lower left corner to return to the old window.
The icons in the new toolbar are also easier to switch and select.
The carving tool group is now integrated into the 3D toolbar to select and switch.
Now that the object window has been fully updated, it is more convenient to change the object type that needs to be adjusted.
You can easily switch between the scene, fabric, sticker, button, eye, line, seal, and secondary options.
Click the icon in the upper left corner of the option card to quickly browse and call the object type in Connect Shop.
Here you can click the icon that you want to add
will be automatically recorded.
Next, let's take a look at the update of the key frame animation of the version.
You can use the fabric used for the versions to K-true.
The K-true version name can help you quickly find the corresponding version in the animation editor
and carry out subsequent operations.
The K-true animation will allow you to control whether the K-true effect is activated or not.
This function is very suitable for the effect of making cloth falling off the frame
or holding the cloth in your hands tightly.
The key frame animation of the K-true is similar to the previous one.
You can change the position of the K-true animation in the scene you want to make
or adjust the various settings in the K-true attribute, such as the sharpness.
You can also use the key frame animation
to change the position of the K-true animation in the scene you want to make.
Here, you can change the position of the K-true animation in the scene you want to make
or adjust the various settings in the scene you want to make.
All you need to do is to set the simulation preset to the user's self-detection.
Then you can K-true the weight and the air resistance.
The K-true animation organization is optimized.
The K-true animation organization has been greatly improved.
A neater, more accurate top structure has been generated.
To show the grid structure more conveniently,
open the display frame,
and then select the grid type of the version to be switched to 4-split.
Compared to the previous version, even if it is a simple T-shirt style, you can also see that the four-sided grid created in the new version is cleaner and neater.
When applying more complex styles of clothing, such as a dresser full of pleats, the new algorithm will calculate a grid arrangement that can maintain the details and structure of the clothing.
3D window display hair effect
In the new version, we have added a material type and hair material.
Whether it is high-quality dyeing, the hair effect can be displayed in the 3D window, and the hair parameters can be used in other 3D software through the USB file format.
You can set the hair display type as round, flat, and short.
You can customize the hair display type according to your needs.
In the hair display type, you can set the hair display type as round, flat, and short.
In the hair display type, you can set the hair display type according to your needs.
You can customize the hair display type according to your needs.
Now, the UV editor supports the UV image of the side and back of the generation and adjustment version.
If you need to adjust the side and back of the UV image, please switch to the dense texture surface first.
Go to the window menu and turn on the UV editor display.
Select the version that needs to be adjusted.
Select the side and back of the UV expansion option in the property bar.
After selecting these options, the UV that will be generated for the selected versions will be generated for the side and back of the UV.
If you need to export the expanded UV, please confirm that you have selected the unified UV coordinate option in the OBJ setting in the export OBJ setting.
Insert the exported file into other 3D software.
You can see that the side and back of the UV are also exported together.
IK joint print
IK joint print will help you to apply Marvelous Designer's pose or animation to the external FBX model.
As long as they use the same set of IK joint point structure, this feature can be fitted to many virtual models downloaded on many platforms, such as DOS3D, Mixamo, Character Creator and MetaHuman.
Enter the FBX file under your T-pose.
and then go to the property editor to find the IK joint print label.
You can manually set the Google joints corresponding to the IK joint,
or choose to automatically print.
After printing, click on the T-shape position.
If the reset position option is correctly activated,
our printing is successfully completed.
Now you can use Marvelous Designer in your virtual model application,
the posture and action files in the sketchbook.
Automatic Transformation
You can download action files from other external platforms,
such as Mixamo,
in Marvelous Designer.
Change to the default virtual model in the matching sketchbook,
or your own virtual model action.
Go to Marvelous Designer,
find the virtual model in the main menu,
then click on the Automatic Transformation as an action option.
Choose to convert the corresponding virtual model type,
and import the FBX file just downloaded.
Click on Transformation to convert the animation it carries
to FBX.
Click on the FBX file,
and save the file.
Now you can apply the action to the default virtual model.
You can also apply this action to the self-defined virtual model
that the IK joint has been introduced before.
Modular Drawing
The new Modular Drawing is a function that integrates and optimizes
the previous modular controller and modular editor.
Now you can manage all the clothing modules
through a simple structure.
After opening the Modular Drawing,
you can click on the arrow
to hide or open it.
In the previous version,
the modules were registered through the modular editor,
and they need to be used through the modular compiler.
Now you can directly register the module components in the Modular Drawing.
The structure of the Modular Drawing is as follows,
group type,
style,
component.
This structure makes it more convenient for you to organize and manage all kinds of style designs.
When you click on the product line in the upper right corner of the style,
the style group button will appear.
You can see the production line file folder named window.
The production line file folder is used as the sub-particle of the sub-particle.
It is used to classify those styles.
After naming,
a production line file folder will be generated.
The file folder contains the styles you just saw.
As in the previous version,
the modules in the modular drawing can be added to them
and can be used according to the need to switch the components.
New Drawing window.
The drawing window has been completely updated.
You can manage assets more freely.
All you have to do is click on the icon in the lower left corner
to switch the old version and the new version of the drawing window.
In the new version of the drawing window,
you can browse the assets built into the software
and the assets in the store.
Free products can be directly downloaded and used in the background.
You can switch free and all products according to your needs.
Under the class set label,
you can download and upload to the cloud platform.
You can also download and upload to the cloud platform.
You can download and upload to the cloud platform.
Now the search and application files are more smooth than before.
You can directly call for available documents or materials.
Click on the addition button next to the class set icon.
You can add the custom assets.
After adding the file to the custom draft,
you can quickly call for assets in these files.
The screenshot preview effect in the new draft window is also more intuitive.
Style model rendering
In the 3D window rendering option,
This rendering style is a rendering style that emphasizes the lines, and it looks like a 2D style picture.
You can adjust the outline line, sewing line, internal line, and the thickness and thickness of the bright line.
You can also adjust the color of the line to match different styles.
Compared to the usual 3D rendering, this is a good way to see the clothing pattern and design details at a glance.
You can set the background picture to pure green, so it can be used as a green wood.
Then turn on the video capture, capture the animation in the 3D window.
This is a simple way to create a video, you can use these video materials in the demonstration, promotional video, etc.
Double head zipper
Now the zipper type can be selected as a double head zipper.
Click on the zipper or zipper, go to the property editor.
Under the type selection, select double.
Both sides of the zipper can be pulled, you can adjust the position of the zipper according to your needs.
You can choose two zippers, two heads are the same or two heads are the same.
OBJ zipper pre-set
Now we support the pre-set zipper zipper to be replaced with OBJ zipper.
According to your needs, you can adjust the position of the zipper.
Or use a more three-dimensional OBJ zipper to get a more realistic effect.
Virtual model editor optimization
Now all functions related to virtual models have been integrated into the virtual model editor.
For example, the creative wearing function has been moved from the 3D tool bar to this place for integrated management.
Now the tool division is clearer, and it is more effective to choose.
Double-head zipper
Now you can use a zipper to fix the zipper.
When creating a zipper, you can choose to find the right position on the 3D clothing or 2D tabletop.
In the 3D window, the creation will be more intuitive, and in the 2D tabletop, the creation will be more accurate.
In addition, when recording animation now, the simulation effect of the zipper will also be recorded.
For example, you need to get a more accurate and smoother simulation effect.
When the action is faster, it is recommended to change the scene time and then start recording.
Combined with the function previously introduced, it is a way to add accessories, apply model actions, and record the final animation for clothing.
Automatic adjustment version update
Now the automatic adjustment version function has been optimized.
You can add additional clothing and apply the automatic adjustment version function, which does not affect the clothing you have worn before.
This update will improve the convenience and flexibility of the automatic adjustment version function.
Automatic closure
The automatic closure function has been added under the Everywhere function.
Through the automatic closure function, you can quickly close the opening position of the clothing and brush the cover on the hidden grid.
When you choose the original disk option, the separation and closure areas are simpler.
The original disk is the closure area.
When you choose the 3D brush option, you can draw a line on the clothing.
The brush path will be closed according to the drawing path.
After automatic closure, you can continue to complete the subsequent multidirectional grid optimization in Everywhere.
Binding bone grid
UV fill and baking material